Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Wizard King Julius Novachrono had successfully shielded the people of Clover from an assault by Licht, leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
But his courageous act came at a heavy cost.
What happened here? Tell me, fangents!
Salutations, Yami, is it? You may call me Licht.
Yami attempted to launch a counterattack.
Dark magic. Now dark cloaked.
Dimension Slash!
But Licht escaped. And, as for Julius...
I'm leaving the rest to you now.
Yes, sir.
This is where we must bid each other farewell.
The Great Rebirth will start with you.
Only now is Licht finally beginning to reveal his true intentions for this world.
Nintendo World.
Oh...
何年先だって語って 信じたいから今笑って
愛も愛も愛 確かな約束が欲しくて
楽しくなりそうな方へ 一緒に走っていこうね
いつの間にか君の背中へ 遠く感じてる
青い空にショースが揺れる
Life are flowered in blue
We fear crying in black
We keep waiting
Wait till wait
Bye bye
Don't try to walk away
We try again
Just wait and wait
ière to Eastern place
I'm sorry
Let pouco from our Newmanza
果たしたい僕の気持ちが本当のことね
Baby, if I lie
Wow, I can't believe it
Licked and his sword magic have been chosen by the four-leaf clover grimoire
What's so exciting, Mom?
Well, my dear
Only a select few can get a grimoire like that
And it comes with an extra helping of good luck
Oh
Licked in his four-leaf grimoire
Wow, he's so cool
There you are
This kid again?
Look, stop coming over here and bugging us every day
It's such a pain
Get lost
I'm not here because I wanted to hang out with you
What'd you say, Shorty?
Oh, I don't mind if he stays, Raya
This isn't a bother to me at all
Thank you for stopping by
I'm glad you're here
Whatever
What do you think about all this?
You know, there's been a lot of talk about humans planning to attack us
I'm sure it's a rumor
It's still a possibility though, isn't it?
I mean, think
The human race is so wicked and mean-spirited
They slaughter animals for the sport of it
Without ever giving it a second thought
They don't have much power on their own
But a big group can be dangerous when they get carried away
Even though we elves help them recover from natural disasters
A long time ago
They're probably afraid
What?
Both sides are afraid
We have things in common, but we fear what we don't know
Regardless of that
This land blesses everyone equally with magical grimoires
So, why wouldn't we understand each other?
What's that thing?
A tornado of natural mana running wild
It's awfully big, isn't it?
Yeah, but it should die down on its own
Man, talk about a pain
What's that?
What's he doing?
Looks like there's someone inside the tornado
Yeah, it does
Sword magic
Now, origin flash
Light magic
Lamp of Avior
He's okay
Licht is amazing stopping that big thing
But wait
That light mage was using spells that were just as powerful as his are
I wonder who that guy is
You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine
Thank you for saving me
Tatia, don't leave the castle like that
I'm sorry
Besides, a wind magic user like you
Isn't supposed to be getting herself caught in a mana tornado
What were you thinking?
Thank you for helping my sister
It's no...
Hey, look at his grimoire
It's a four-leaf just like yours
But he's human
Lick's been spending quite a lot of time with those two lately
You can say that again
Seems like he's happy to have some human friends
But hey
They really are good people
Apparently they have the same idea about society that he does
Idea?
They all believe that humans and elves can figure out how to live together peacefully
Ah, is that so
It's odd to see an elf making friends with humans
But if he's doing it
Then I guess it must not be such a bad thing
Besides
That light mage was good enough to be chosen by the four-leaf clover grimoire too
So they're not that different
Let's foster understanding
Your elvish mana really is a remarkable thing
If we combine that with our own magic item technology
This land will be safer and more prosperous
Let's all work together, hand in hand
Is it true? You're with child?
With you for parents, it'll be a lovely baby
Hey, congrats, Tetya
And you too, I guess
Well, thank you for including me, Raya
What are you pouting about, Tiny?
It's nothing
You're still little
You'll understand one day
Would you shut up?
Stop talking down to me like I'm some stupid baby
Excuse me then, big man
Oh, hey, there you are
Hello, Raya
Let me guess, waking up is a pain too now?
You're the worst
Aw, get off my case
Oh, and Potri
I can see you're still clinging on to Licht like nobody's business
He's gonna belong to a human after tomorrow's big ceremony
So you better start letting go of him
Leave me alone, Raya
That's my choice to make, not yours
Hey, watch your tone
It's alright
Even after we get married, Licht will still belong to everybody
Man, you human princesses are so generous
I'd be careful of what I promise if I were you, though, Tetya
Before long, there won't be any room in his busy schedule to spend time with you
You don't have to be so blunt about things
Potri knows what to expect
So what's it like, knowing that you'll be a father in a few months' time?
I can sense that the mana has blessed our lives as well
When our child arrives, we know that your kind will welcome it, and we're very grateful
This little one here is the key to our future
The bridge to unite elves in humankind
Good luck! We wish you the best!
Congratulations!
Thank you all very much
Take care of her
Okay, Licht?
Yes
I swear I'll keep her safe no matter what
My friends, thank you for joining us
Come to think of it, aren't you receiving your grimoire tomorrow?
Wow, you remembered?
Well, how could I forget something so important?
I look forward to seeing what kind of grimoire chooses you as its owner
Me too!
How sweet!
I want to be a bride
I'm sure you'll meet your soulmate one day too, Fauna
Yeah, and hopefully soon
May the rest of your days be happy ones
Thank you
And you better tell me if this guy's unfaithful
I'll smack him around for you
Raya, don't say that
Ah, it's all in fun
He looks like he's really happy
But to tell the truth, he kind of always looked happy
I hate to admit it
But it seems like the ones who have made him even happier are her and that other human
Let's foster understanding
I wonder
Can we really come to understand each other like he said we could?
Licht believes it's possible
Maybe they're right
Elves and human beings
Living side by side
What's going on?
It's the humans, they're attacking us!
Everyone, this way!
Let's hurry!
My spells won't work
Our magic
It's been sealed away
Get down!
You have to get away from here
Hateful humans
This is life magic
Does that mean?
No, this is a mistake
It's not true
I won't accept it
Please, stay with me
Open your eyes
What's happening?
It's been a dream
You can't die
You've been a dream
No, I refuse to believe it
It's not real
None of this is real
No, no, no
No way, no way, no way, no way, no way
People won't accept it
I will never
Forgive
You are
Is that you, Ligt?
Answer me
Ligt
What is this place?
What happened to me?
I thought
I was dead
These hands
They're not mine
I look like
Ligt
What is this?
Have I become him somehow?
Did my spirit
Implant itself in his body?
That's not it
Judging by how this mana feels
The body I'm in is human
A human that looks like Ligt
I see
So I really did die
Whatever Ligt unleashed when our magic was sealed away
It must have been some kind of forbidden spell
And something extremely powerful too
Like reincarnation magic
This light
I can sense them
Every single one
I can feel Raya's soul and the souls of all the other elves in this village
Ligt must have done this in the final few seconds of his life
And all for the sake of our people
But so far
It seems like I'm the only one who's been completely revived
Oh yeah
His grimoire
It chose to bond with Ligt
The soul that truly belongs inside this body
So I won't be able to use it
I'm not sure whether or not this was meant to happen to me
But I am the only one who came back to life
Not only that
But I came back looking like Ligt
I'm the only one who can save the rest of the elves
Which means
I have been chosen
I'll become Ligt
No matter what it takes
I'll revive all the elves
As for the humans
For going back on their word
For killing the people I loved
They must pay
I swear they will all be annihilated
Forbidden magic
Evil Eye
Ah
It would appear you're finally awake
This human has a similar wavelength
So I've imbued your soul with magic from the other world
To support your reincarnation into this body
Gathering enough magic power to make that possible
Wasn't easy you know
So please don't cause me any more trouble
Okay Raya
Wait you're Potri
Why are you
But your old friend Ligt can revive everyone
That's the mission that he
No I must fulfill
You get it
Don't you
Yeah Ligt
I hear ya
You're here too
Raya
About time sleepyhead
Rise and shine
It was good to sleep in
But five more minutes would have been great
As you can see
I've also resurrected these two
Veto
You were a gentle soul who loved to befriend animals
Yet this world has shown you only cruelty
Live with me
As you once did
It is not you who should be despairing
But those unconscionable humans
You must remember your true self
What a tragedy
To think we were once friends
I suppose the world never changes
If humans are so determined to harm each other
Then we'll just help them along
However
You're going to need your body
So let's keep you alive
Fauna
Your appearances are so similar
And you share the same name
This can't be coincidence
There is no need for you to suffer the same sad fate in this age
Now
Awaken
So these three are the souls I was able to restore at this juncture
It's as if they never died
But I'll need greater power to bring back the rest
And that means supplying even more sacrifices
To that end
We will gather the magic stones that were once kept within our village
But have since been scattered far and wide
And we'll use humans to do it
Smart, don't you think?
Oh yeah
Agreed
Let's begin
We'll get back at those hateful scum
I'll make sure they suffer endless despair
Indeed
The Great Rebirth will start with the humans
Wait
We're going to kick off the rebirth?
You're singing a different tune than you used to
I thought this was the part where we get a huge power boost
I see what's going on
You tricked us, didn't you?
Now what?
It can't be
From the very moment I gathered you three to serve as my allies
You were marked as sacrifices for this forbidden magic
And now it's time that you receive your true names
Forbidden magic
You're kidding me
What makes you think I'm going to go by whatever random off-the-wall name you throw at me, huh?
I'm Rady Spirito and that's that!
No, Master Lentz, please don't!
I just can't believe this all this time
I thought we were your most cherished friends
Yes, you truly were
Then why?
I needed you
After all, you're the sacrificial lambs who will bring back my real friends
You're very dear to me
Damn you, Lentz!
Lentz!
What's wrong?
On To more
yeah
i don't need no money
i don't need no
魔力はいらない
自力で挑んだ
ミラクル
起きること
願い
微力ながら
1mmずつ
ビリビリ
切り込んでく
世界を巻き込んでく
my disabilities
my ability
逆に
それが
俺のエネルギー
どうしても
自らを
見失って
嫌いに
Maybe if you
CLOVER CLIPS
CLOVER CLOVER CLIPS
Thank you.